Guide to the Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
- Chapter Records, 1928-2002; 1928 2002; 71.5 linear feet
  - Virginia State University
    - Correspondence, 1971-1995 (Box 3.125, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports, 1972-1996 (Box 3.125, Folder 9)
  - Wabash Valley
    - Correspondence, 1978-1995 (Box 3.126, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1976-1996 (Box 3.126, Folder 2)
  - Wake Forest University
    - Correspondence, 1974-1995 (Box 3.126, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1965-1996 (Box 3.126, Folder 4)
  - Washington State University
    - Correspondence, 1956-1995 (Box 3.126, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1962-1996 (Box 3.126, Folder 6)
  - Washington University
    - Correspondence, 1957-1975 (Box 3.126, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1989 (Box 3.126, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports, 1956-1996 (Box 3.126, Folder 9)
  - Waterways Experiment Station
    - Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 3.126, Folder 10)
    - Annual Reports, 1992-1996 (Box 3.126, Folder 11)
  - Wayne State University
    - Correspondence, 1956-1976 (Box 3.126, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1977-1995 (Box 3.126, Folder 13)
    - Annual Reports, 1958-1996 (Box 3.126, Folder 14)
  - Weber State College
    - Correspondence, 1974-1995 (Box 3.126, Folder 15)
    - Annual Reports, 1969-1996 (Box 3.126, Folder 16)
  - Wellesley College
    - Correspondence, 1956-1995 (Box 3.127, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1957-1996 (Box 3.127, Folder 2)
  - Wesleyan University
    - Correspondence, 1959-1988 (Box 3.127, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1957-1996 (Box 3.127, Folder 4)
  - West Chester University
    - Correspondence, 1983-1991 (Box 3.127, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1984-1989 (Box 3.127, Folder 6)
  - West Texas State University
    - Correspondence, 1965-1994 (Box 3.127, Folder 7)
    - Annual Reports, 1967-1993 (Box 3.127, Folder 8)
  - West Virginia University
    - Correspondence, 1956-1974 (Box 3.127, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1995 (Box 3.127, Folder 10)
    - Annual Reports, 1957-1996 (Box 3.127, Folder 11)
  - Westchester
    - Correspondence, 1979-1995 (Box 3.127, Folder 12)
    - Annual Reports, 1978-1996 (Box 3.127, Folder 13)
  - Western Carolina University
    - Correspondence, 1967-1995 (Box 3.127, Folder 14)
    - Annual Reports, 1968-1996 (Box 3.127, Folder 15)
  - Western Connecticut State University
    - Correspondence, 1976-1995 (Box 3.128, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1979-1996 (Box 3.128, Folder 2)
  - Western Illinois University
    - Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 3.128, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, 1973-1998 (Box 3.128, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1996 (Box 3.128, Folder 5)
  - Western Kentucky University
    - Correspondence, 1966-1972 (Box 3.128, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1974-1995 (Box 3.128, Folder 7)
    - Annual Reports, 1967-1973 (Box 3.128, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports, 1974-1996 (Box 3.128, Folder 9)
  - Western Maryland College
    - Correspondence, 1970-1995 (Box 3.129, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1996 (Box 3.129, Folder 2)
  - Western Pennsylvania
    - Correspondence, 1966-1995 (Box 3.129, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1971-1996 (Box 3.129, Folder 4)
  - Western Washington State College
    - Correspondence, 1965-1995 (Box 3.129, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1968-1996 (Box 3.129, Folder 6)
  - Western Washington Research and Extension Center
    - Correspondence, 1958-1970 (Box 3.129, Folder 7)
    - Annual Reports, 1959-1971 (Box 3.129, Folder 8)
  - Whirlpool
    - Correspondence, 1974-1995 (Box 3.129, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports, 1973-1980 (Box 3.129, Folder 10)
    - Annual Reports, 1980-1984 (Box 3.13, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1984-1991 (Box 3.13, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1991-1996 (Box 3.13, Folder 3)
  - Whitman College
    - Correspondence, 1962-1995 (Box 3.13, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports, 1972-1983 (Box 3.13, Folder 5)
  - Wichita State University
    - Correspondence, 1964-1995 (Box 3.13, Folder 6)
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1996 (Box 3.13, Folder 7)
  - Wilkes University
    - Correspondence, 1966-1995 (Box 3.13, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports, 1968-1984 (Box 3.131, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1984-1996 (Box 3.131, Folder 2)
  - William Patterson College of New Jersey
    - Correspondence, 1987-1995 (Box 3.131, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1988-1997 (Box 3.131, Folder 4)
  - Williams College
    - Correspondence, 1968-1995 (Box 3.131, Folder 5)
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1996 (Box 3.131, Folder 6)
  - Wittenburg University
    - Correspondence, 1962-1995 (Box 3.131, Folder 7)
    - Annual Reports, 1974-1996 (Box 3.131, Folder 8)
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution
    - Correspondence, 1983-1995 (Box 3.131, Folder 9)
    - Annual Reports, 1989-1996 (Box 3.131, Folder 10)
  - Wooster, Ohio
    - Correspondence, 1958-1995 (Box 3.131, Folder 11)
    - Annual Reports, 1959-1963 (Box 3.132, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1964-1967 (Box 3.132, Folder 2)
    - Annual Reports, 1968-1974 (Box 3.132, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1974-1984 (Box 3.132, Folder 4)
    - Annual Reports, 1984-1996 (Box 3.132, Folder 5)
  - Worcester Polytechnic Institute
    - Correspondence, 1956-1994 (Box 3.132, Folder 6)
    - Annual Reports, 1963-1996 (Box 3.132, Folder 7)
  - Wright State University
    - Correspondence, 1968-1995 (Box 3.132, Folder 8)
    - Annual Reports, 1969-1996 (Box 3.132, Folder 9)
  - Yale University
    - Correspondence, 1957-1995 (Box 3.133, Folder 1)
    - Annual Reports, 1956-1996 (Box 3.133, Folder 2)
    - Sigma Xi Executives Visits to Major Research Universities, 1994 (Box 3.139, Folder 5)
  - York College of the City University of New York
    - Correspondence, 1968-1995 (Box 3.133, Folder 3)
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1996 (Box 3.133, Folder 4)
  - Youngstown State University
    - Correspondence, 1969-1984 (Box 3.133, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1985-1995 (Box 3.133, Folder 6)
    - Annual Reports, 1970-1996 (Box 3.133, Folder 7)
  - Chapters-At-Large
    - Correspondence, Jul. 1975 (Box 3.134, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Aug. 1975 (Box 3.134, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Sep. 1975 (Box 3.134, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Oct. 1975 (Box 3.134, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Nov. 1975 (Box 3.134, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Dec. 1975 (Box 3.134, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Jan. 1976 (Box 3.134, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Feb. 1976 (Box 3.134, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Mar. 1976 (Box 3.134, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Apr. 1976 (Box 3.134, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, May 1976 (Box 3.134, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Jun. 1976 (Box 3.134, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Jul. 1-23, 1976 (Box 3.134, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Jul. 24-31, 1976 (Box 3.134, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Aug. 1976 (Box 3.135, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Sep. 1976 (Box 3.135, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Oct. 1976 (Box 3.135, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Nov. 1976 (Box 3.135, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Dec. 1976 (Box 3.135, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Jan.-Apr. 1977 (Box 3.135, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, May-Aug. 1977 (Box 3.135, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Sep.-Dec. 1977 (Box 3.135, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Jan.-Apr. 1978 (Box 3.135, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, May-Jul. 1978 (Box 3.135, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Aug. 1978 (Box 3.135, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Sep. 1978 (Box 3.135, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Oct.-Dec. 1978 (Box 3.135, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1979 (Box 3.135, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Mar.-Apr. 1979 (Box 3.135, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, May 1979 (Box 3.135, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Jun. 1979 (Box 3.135, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Jul. 1979 (Box 3.136, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Aug. 1979 (Box 3.136, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Sep. 1979 (Box 3.136, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Oct. 1979 (Box 3.136, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Nov. 1979 (Box 3.136, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Dec. 1979 (Box 3.136, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Jan.-Feb. 1980 (Box 3.136, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Mar. 1980 (Box 3.136, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Apr. 1980 (Box 3.136, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, May 1980 (Box 3.136, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Jun. 1980 (Box 3.136, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Jul. 1-16, 1980 (Box 3.136, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Jul. 17-31, 1980 (Box 3.136, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Aug. 1980 (Box 3.136, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Sep. 1980 (Box 3.136, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Oct. 1980 (Box 3.136, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Nov. 1980 (Box 3.136, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Dec. 1980 (Box 3.136, Folder 18)
  - International Chapters
    - Correspondence, Jan. 1977 (Box 3.136, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Feb. 1977 (Box 3.136, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Mar. 1977 (Box 3.136, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, Apr. 1977 (Box 3.137, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, May 1977 (Box 3.137, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, Jun. 1977 (Box 3.137, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence, Jul. 1977 (Box 3.137, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, Aug. 1977 (Box 3.137, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Sep. 1977 (Box 3.137, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Oct. 1977 (Box 3.137, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Nov. 1977 (Box 3.137, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Dec. 1977 (Box 3.137, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Jan. 1978 (Box 3.137, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, Feb. 1-16, 1978 (Box 3.137, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, Feb. 17-28, 1978 (Box 3.137, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, Mar. 1-7, 1978 (Box 3.137, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, Mar. 7-31, 1978 (Box 3.137, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, Apr.-May 1978 (Box 3.137, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, Jun. 1978 (Box 3.137, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence, Jul. 1978 (Box 3.137, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, Aug.-Dec. 1978 (Box 3.137, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Jul.-Aug. 1981 (Box 3.137, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Sep.-Oct. 1981 (Box 3.137, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, Nov.-Dec. 1981 (Box 3.137, Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Building Fund, 1974-1975 (Box 3.142, Folder 6)
    - Calling All Presidents Program, 1994 (Box 3.139, Folder 6)
    - Calling All Presidents Program, 1994 (Box 3.139, Folder 7)
    - Chapter and Club Lists, 1970 (Box 3.139, Folder 8)
    - Chapter and Club Lists, 1971 (Box 3.139, Folder 9)
    - Chapter and Club Lists, 1972 (Box 3.139, Folder 10)
    - Chapter and Club Lists, 1974 (Box 3.139, Folder 11)
    - Chapter and Club Lists, 1976 (Box 3.139, Folder 12)
    - Chapter and Club Lists, 1980 (Box 3.139, Folder 13)
    - Chapter and Club Officers, 1997 (Box 3.139, Folder 14)
    - Chapter and Club Officers, 1997 (Box 3.139, Folder 15)
    - Chapter and Club Officers, 1997 (Box 3.139, Folder 16)
    - Chapter and Club Visits, 1991 (Box 3.14, Folder 1)
    - Chicago Area Sigma Xi, 1984-1986 (Box 3.14, Folder 2)
    - Five Chapter Project, 1982 (Box 3.14, Folder 3)
    - La Jolla Club: Officers, 1970 (Box 3.14, Folder 4)
    - Major Research Universities: Chapter Information, 1992 (Box 3.14, Folder 5)
    - Manual of Procedure for Chapter Officers, 1947 (Box 3.14, Folder 6)
    - Manual of Procedure for Chapter and Club Officers, Jan. 1970 (Box 3.14, Folder 7)
    - Manual of Procedure for Chapter and Club Officers, 1983 (Box 3.14, Folder 8)
    - Manual of Procedure for Chapter and Club Officers, 1987 (Box 3.14, Folder 9)
    - Manual of Procedure for Chapter and Club Officers, 1988 (Box 3.14, Folder 10)
    - Network: Presidents and Secretaries, 1985-1986 (Box 3.14, Folder 11)
    - Network: Presidents and Secretaries, 1988-1989 (Box 3.14, Folder 12)
    - Network: Presidents and Secretaries, 1990-1991 (Box 3.14, Folder 13)
    - Network: Presidents and Secretaries, 1991-1992 (Box 3.14, Folder 14)
    - Network: Presidents and Secretaries, 1992-1993 (Halfbox 3.141, Folder 1)
    - Network: Presidents and Secretaries, 1993-1994 (Halfbox 3.141, Folder 2)
    - Network: Presidents and Secretaries, 1994-1995 (Halfbox 3.141, Folder 3)
    - New Traditions: Program Ideas for Chapters and Clubs, 1986 (Halfbox 3.141, Folder 4)
    - Newsletter for Chapter and Club Officers, 1973-1982 (Halfbox 3.141, Folder 5)
    - Non-Academic Group Workshop, 10 Oct. 1992 (Halfbox 3.141, Folder 6)
    - Officers' Handbook, 1990-1991 (Halfbox 3.141, Folder 7)
    - Officers' Handbook, 1992-1994 (Halfbox 3.141, Folder 8)
    - Officers' Handbook, 1994-1995 (Halfbox 3.141, Folder 9)
    - Southeast Texas Sigma Xi Council: Minutes, 1984 (Halfbox 3.141, Folder 10)
    - Southeast Texas Sigma Xi Council: Minutes, Jan. - Aug. 1985 (Halfbox 3.141, Folder 11)
    - Southeast Texas Sigma Xi Council: Minutes, Sep. - Dec. 1985 (Halfbox 3.141, Folder 12)
    - Southeast Texas Sigma Xi Council: Minutes, Jan. - Apr. 1986 (Box 3.142, Folder 1)
    - Southeast Texas Sigma Xi Council: Minutes, May - Oct. 1986 (Box 3.142, Folder 2)
    - Southeast Texas Sigma Xi Council: Minutes, Nov. 1986 - Apr. 1987 (Box 3.142, Folder 3)
    - Southeast Texas Sigma Xi Council: Minutes, May 1987 - Aug. 1989 (Box 3.142, Folder 4)
- Annual Meetings Records, 1959-1999; 1959 1999; 33.5 linear feet
  This series contains files related to the planning and conducting of Sigma Xi's annual meeting and forum. Meetings were held once a year, with the exception of 1997, when meetings were held in both March and November. No records are present for the 1992 meeting.
  - 1959
    - Agenda (Box 4.001, Folder 1)
  - 1960
    - Agenda (Box 4.001, Folder 2)
  - 1961
    - Agenda (Box 4.001, Folder 3)
  - 1962
    - Agenda (Box 4.001, Folder 4)
  - 1963
    - Agenda (Box 4.001, Folder 5)
  - 1964
    - Agenda (Box 4.001, Folder 6)
  - 1965
    - Agenda (Box 4.001, Folder 7)
  - 1966
    - Agenda (Box 4.001, Folder 8)
  - 1967
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.001, Folder 9)
    - Committee on the 1967 Annual Meeting (Box 4.001, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence, 1966 (Box 4.001, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 4.001, Folder 12)
    - Expenses (Box 4.001, Folder 13)
    - Photographs (Box 4.001, Folder 14)
  - 1968
    - Agenda (Box 4.001, Folder 15)
    - Agenda (Box 4.001, Folder 16)
    - Committee on 1968 Annual Meeting (Box 4.001, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 4.001, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, Jan.-May 1968 (Box 4.001, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, Jun.-Sep. 1968 (Box 4.002, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, Oct.-Dec. 1968 (Box 4.002, Folder 2)
    - Expenses (Box 4.002, Folder 3)
    - Publicity/Program (Box 4.002, Folder 4)
  - 1969
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.002, Folder 5)
    - Committee on the 1969 Meeting (Box 4.002, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 4.002, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 4.002, Folder 8)
    - Expenses (Box 4.002, Folder 9)
    - Materials Distributed (Box 4.002, Folder 10)
    - Publicity (Box 4.002, Folder 11)
    - Publicity (Box 4.002, Folder 12)
    - Questionnaire (Box 4.002, Folder 13)
    - Speakers (Box 4.002, Folder 14)
  - 1970
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.003, Folder 1)
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.003, Folder 2)
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.003, Folder 3)
    - Committee on 1970 Annual Meeting (Box 4.003, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 4.003, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, Jan.-Jun. 1970 (Box 4.003, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, Jul.-Nov. 1970 (Box 4.003, Folder 7)
    - Expenses (Box 4.003, Folder 8)
    - Publicity (Box 4.003, Folder 9)
    - Speakers, Biographies and Pictures (Box 4.003, Folder 10)
    - Speakers, Speeches (Box 4.003, Folder 11)
  - 1971
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.003, Folder 12)
    - Committee on 1971 Annual Meeting (Box 4.003, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.004, Folder 1)
    - Photographs (Box 4.004, Folder 2)
  - 1972
    - Photographs and Program (Box 4.004, Folder 3)
  - 1973
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.004, Folder 4)
    - Agenda/Program, Proceedings of the 74th National Meeting (Box 4.004, Folder 5)
    - Agenda/Program, Report of Officers and Chairmen of Standing Committees to 74th National Meeting (Box 4.004, Folder 6)
    - Committee on 1973 Meeting (Box 4.004, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, Feb. 1970-Jul. 1973 (Box 4.004, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, Aug. 1973 (Box 4.004, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence, Sep.-Nov. 1973 (Box 4.004, Folder 10)
    - Parliamentarian (Box 4.004, Folder 11)
    - Proceedings of the Seventy-Fourth National Meeting, 5-8 Oct. 1973 (Box 4.063, Folder 16)
    - Publicity (Box 4.004, Folder 12)
    - Questionnaire (Box 4.004, Folder 13)
    - Resolution Committee (Box 4.004, Folder 14)
    - Speakers - Biographies, Pictures, and Speeches (Box 4.004, Folder 15)
    - Speakers - Biographies, Pictures, and Speeches (Box 4.004, Folder 16)
  - 1974
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.005, Folder 1)
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.005, Folder 2)
    - Committee on the 1974 Annual Meeting (Box 4.005, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.005, Folder 4)
    - Photographs of 1974 Annual Meeting (Box 4.005, Folder 5)
    - Proceedings of the Seventy-Fifth National Meeting, 1-4 Nov. 1974 (Box 4.063, Folder 17)
    - Publicity (Box 4.005, Folder 6)
    - Questionnaire (Box 4.005, Folder 7)
    - Regional Committees (Box 4.005, Folder 8)
    - Resolutions Committee (Box 4.005, Folder 9)
    - Speakers (Box 4.005, Folder 10)
  - 1975
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.005, Folder 11)
    - Agenda/Program, Reports (Box 4.005, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.005, Folder 13)
    - Photographs (Box 4.005, Folder 14)
    - Publicity (Box 4.005, Folder 15)
    - Questionnaire (Box 4.006, Folder 1)
    - Regional Committees (Box 4.006, Folder 2)
    - Resolutions Committee (Box 4.006, Folder 3)
    - Science and Society Program (Box 4.006, Folder 4)
    - Speakers (Box 4.006, Folder 5)
  - 1976
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.006, Folder 6)
    - Agenda/Program, Reports (Box 4.006, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 15 Jan. 1973-31 Aug. 1976 (Box 4.006, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence, 1 Sep. 1976-16 Feb. 1977 (Box 4.006, Folder 9)
    - Photographs (Box 4.006, Folder 10)
    - Proceedings of the Seventy-Seventh Annual Meeting, 5-8 Nov. 1976 (Box 4.064, Folder 1)
    - Publicity (Box 4.006, Folder 11)
    - Regional Committees (Box 4.006, Folder 12)
    - Resolutions Committee (Box 4.006, Folder 13)
    - Science and Society (Box 4.006, Folder 14)
    - Speakers (Box 4.006, Folder 15)
  - 1977
    - Agenda/Program, Agenda and Reports of Officers and Chairmen of Standing Committees (Box 4.006, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.006, Folder 17)
    - Questionnaire (Box 4.006, Folder 18)
    - Regional Committees (Box 4.006, Folder 19)
  - 1978
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.007, Folder 1)
    - Agenda/Program, Proceedings (Box 4.007, Folder 2)
    - Committee on Regional Committees (Box 4.007, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.007, Folder 4)
    - Nominations (Box 4.007, Folder 5)
    - Photographs (Box 4.007, Folder 6)
    - Proceedings of the Seventy-Ninth Annual Meeting, 27-30 Oct. 1978 (Box 4.064, Folder 2)
    - Publicity (Box 4.007, Folder 7)
    - Questionnaire (Box 4.007, Folder 8)
    - Regional Committees (Box 4.007, Folder 9)
    - Resolutions Committee (Box 4.007, Folder 10)
    - Speakers (Box 4.007, Folder 11)
  - 1979
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.007, Folder 12)
    - Agenda/Program, Proceedings (Box 4.007, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 4 Dec. 1978-30 Aug. 1979 (Box 4.007, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 31 Aug.-27 Nov. 1979 (Box 4.008, Folder 1)
    - Poster Session (Box 4.008, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings of the Eightieth Annual Meeting, 19-22 Oct. 1979 (Box 4.064, Folder 3)
    - Questionnaire (Box 4.008, Folder 3)
    - Regional Committees (Box 4.008, Folder 4)
    - Resolutions Committee (Box 4.008, Folder 5)
    - Speakers (Box 4.008, Folder 6)
  - 1980
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.008, Folder 7)
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.008, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Regional Committees (Box 4.008, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.008, Folder 10)
    - Poster Session (Box 4.008, Folder 11)
    - Proceedings of the Eighty-First Annual Meeting, 10-13 Oct. 1980 (Box 4.064, Folder 4)
    - Questionnaire (Box 4.008, Folder 12)
    - Regional Committees (Box 4.008, Folder 13)
    - Speakers (Box 4.008, Folder 14)
  - 1981
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.008, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.008, Folder 16)
    - Poster Session (Box 4.008, Folder 17)
    - Proceedings of the Eighty-Second Annual Meeting, 16-19 Oct. 1981 (Box 4.064, Folder 5)
    - Publicity (Box 4.008, Folder 18)
    - Regional Committee (Box 4.009, Folder 1)
    - Resolution Committee (Box 4.009, Folder 2)
    - Science and Society Program (Box 4.009, Folder 3)
    - Speakers (Box 4.009, Folder 4)
  - 1982
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.009, Folder 5)
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.009, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.009, Folder 7)
    - Expenses (Box 4.009, Folder 8)
    - Proceedings of the Eighty-Third Annual Meeting, 22-25 Oct. 1982 (Box 4.064, Folder 6)
    - Regional Committees (Box 4.009, Folder 9)
    - Science and Society Program (Box 4.009, Folder 10)
    - Speakers and Guests (Box 4.009, Folder 11)
  - 1983
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.009, Folder 12)
    - Agenda and Report of Officers and Chairmen of Standing Committee (Box 4.009, Folder 13)
    - Committee on Regions (Box 4.009, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.009, Folder 15)
    - Photographs (Box 4.009, Folder 16)
    - Proceedings of the Eighty-Fourth Annual Meeting, 28-31 Oct. 1983 (Box 4.064, Folder 7)
    - Publicity (Box 4.009, Folder 17)
    - Questionnaire (Box 4.009, Folder 18)
    - Regional Committee (Box 4.009, Folder 19)
    - Speakers (Box 4.009, Folder 20)
    - Speakers, Proctor Prize Recipient (Box 4.01, Folder 1)
    - Workshop (Box 4.01, Folder 2)
  - 1984
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.01, Folder 3)
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.01, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.01, Folder 5)
    - Proceedings of the Eighty-Fifth Annual Meeting, 19-22 Oct. 1984 (Box 4.064, Folder 8)
    - Questionnaire (Box 4.01, Folder 6)
    - Regional Committee (Box 4.01, Folder 7)
    - Slides (Slidebox 4.067)
    - Speakers (Box 4.01, Folder 8)
  - 1985
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.01, Folder 9)
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.01, Folder 10)
    - Agenda/Program, Publications (Box 4.01, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Annual Meetings (Box 4.01, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.01, Folder 13)
    - Expenses (Box 4.01, Folder 14)
    - Honorary Members (Box 4.011, Folder 1)
    - McGovern Lecturer: Gerald Holton (Box 4.064, Folder 9)
    - Proceedings of the Eighty-Sixth Annual Meeting, 18-21 Oct. 1985 (Box 4.064, Folder 10)
    - Questionnaire (Box 4.011, Folder 2)
    - Record of Sigma Xi Film and Videotape Activity with Chapters and Clubs, 1985-1987 (Box 4.064, Folder 11)
    - Record of Sigma Xi Film and Videotape Activity with Chapters and Clubs, 1985-1987 (Box 4.065, Folder 1)
    - Regional Committees, Mid-Atlantic - Northeast (Box 4.011, Folder 3)
    - Regional Committees, Northwest - Southwest (Box 4.011, Folder 4)
    - Speakers (Box 4.011, Folder 5)
    - Speakers, Proctor Prize Recipient (Box 4.011, Folder 6)
  - 1986
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.011, Folder 9)
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.011, Folder 10)
    - Agenda/Program (Box 4.039, Folder 6)
    - Agenda/Program, Publications (Box 4.011, Folder 11)
    - Committee on Centennial Meeting (Box 4.011, Folder 12)
    - Cornell, Agenda/Program (Box 4.011, Folder 7)
    - Cornell, Correspondence (Box 4.011, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.011, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence (Box 4.039, Folder 7)
    - General Information (Box 4.039, Folder 8)
    - Photographs (Box 4.039, Folder 9)
    - Photographs: Centennial Lecturers (Box 4.066, Folder 9)
    - Planning (Box 4.039, Folder 10)
    - Proceedings of the Eighty-Seventh Annual Meeting, 23-26 Oct. 1986 (Box 4.065, Folder 2)